Zoltan Almodo

JavaScript, React, Node.js web developer based in London, UK

Profile

I enjoy solving problems, enthusiastic about programming and learning new technologies.

Happy to work with others and share different views in development with a strong attitude towards finding the best solutions.

My Education and experience in Product Design, Design Management and Visual Communications allow me to work closely with designers and design assets, to understand and modify UX, branding and communication strategies, and to comprehend and advise on business requirements.

I work cooperatively maintaining clear and constant communication with others. I am organized, responsible and open to new ideas, respectfully considering the viewpoints of other people through active listening. I am able to coordinate tasks based on priority while focusing on the end result.

Projects

OneDeko Ltd. London: website / web-shop design, maintenance and social promotions:

https://twitter.com/onedeko?lang=en

Anuka Kid: overall design and programming, custom theme add-ons, added extra functionality and installed Card payment, Google Analytics, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript https://anukakid.com/

Andrea Ovari textile designer: website design and programming, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript http://www.ovariandrea.hu/

Doodle Disco: HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript https://zoltanalmodo.github.io/Doodle-Disco/

Random Phrase Generator: Javascript, HTML, CSS, DOM manipulation

https://codepen.io/zoltanalmodo/pen/oMymYx

Kodflix app: Javascript, React, npm, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB

HTML, CSS / Less CSS

https://zoltan-kodflix-ddisco-app.herokuapp.com/ Please wait few seconds for Heroku to load... thank you.

Alpha-team-app: Javascript, React, HTML, CSS https://zoltanalmodo.github.io/alpha-app/

07501 927 004 zoltanalmodo@gmail.com

Github LinkedIn Portfolio

Skills

JavaScript

React Node.js

HTML5

CSS3 / Less CSS

Github

Git

Redux

Mobix

jQuery

ExpressJs

npm

Heroku

Mongo.DB

MySQL

CSV

Photoshop / Illustrator

Premier / Final Cut Pro Figma / Prototyping

Wireframing

UX/UI design

Bootstrap

Product and Web

design

Web-shop design

Web-shop

. Maintenance

Database Management

Managing production

teams

Agile Methodologies

Pair programming

TDD / BDD

Google Analytics

Google Firebase

Experience

Designer, Web Developer: 2012-present

Web-design, Web-shop design, UI/UX design, Graphic design

OneDeko Ltd. London (now Nua-Style) - Web Designer 2009-2017 Web-design, Web-shop design, Web-shop maintenance, Graphic design

Westline Media Ltd. Hungary - *Graphic Designer / Videographer 2004-2008* designing promotional videos / advertising campaigns

Philos Laboratories Software Developer Ltd. Hungary - Computer Games Graphic Design Lead 2000-2002

- computer game graphic designer / concept artist / GUI designer
- team leader of five
- 2d and 3d characters + level concept design, graphical user interface design, using 2d and 3d software packages
- ensuring quality of final products: 3d textured objects, game levels, and graphical user interfaces

Education

KODIRI: Full-stack web-developer

FreeCodeCamp: Online Course JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, React Harvard SC50 online course: Introduction to Computer Science Eloquent JavaScript 3rd edition written by: Marijn Haverbeke

MOME University of Design Budapest:

MA in Design Management 1997-2004

Master of Arts in Product Design 1996-2002

EVENTUS: Computer Graphic design 1995-1996

Interests

MeetUp groups:

kodiri.com, Codecademy London, Js Monthly, Founders & Coders, JavaScript London

Activities:

- I love to travel and experience new cultures.
- I run a foundation and teach programming, drawing, painting, sculpturing for children.

Interests:

- DIY books: programming, gardening, architecture, fashion, woodworking, art
- Biographies : Sir Isaac Newton
- Drawing, Painting, Sculpturing
- Music : Ambient-Mix on MixCloud, Kraftwerk, Chemical Brothers, The Cure, Captain Beefheart & His Magic Band, Le Tigre, Agaskodo Teliverek, PinkFloyd, CSS, Fitness-Mix, Beastie Boys, Trent Reznor